MkvDrama.Org
MkvDrama.Org
Episode 11
11화
Why don't you take a carriage?
마차를 타지 그래요?
I have something to ask the teacher.
선생님께 물어볼 게 있어요.
what?
무엇?
what do you mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
When you said what you said in Garden of Bells?
종의 정원에서 당신이 말한 것을 말했을 때?
still
그래도
Thank you for not sending it to me.
나한테 보내지 않아서 고마워요
To the junior lord of the Wu family.
우 가문의 후배 영주에게.
But you already have a wife.
하지만 당신에게는 이미 아내가 있습니다.
You can ask me to do anything in return.
그 대가로 나에게 무엇이든 해달라고 요청할 수 있습니다.
Except marrying you.
당신과 결혼하는 것 빼고요.
What happens if you don't have a wife?
아내가 없으면 어떻게 되나요?
I am married to Hua Qian. Because she drugged me.
나는 Hua Qian과 결혼했습니다. 왜냐하면 그녀가 나에게 약을 먹였기 때문입니다.
I had to take responsibility.
나는 책임을 져야만 했습니다.
I had no idea I was taking medication.
나는 내가 약을 먹고 있다는 사실을 전혀 몰랐습니다.
I have never touched her.
나는 그녀를 만진 적이 없습니다.
She admitted it herself.
그녀는 스스로 그것을 인정했습니다.
Sounds like something she would do.
그녀가 할 일처럼 들리네요.
Now I know what I want.
이제 나는 내가 원하는 것이 무엇인지 압니다.
give me some time
나에게 시간을 좀 줘.
After my father's case was resolved
아버지 사건이 해결된 후
I will officially divorce her.
나는 그녀와 정식으로 이혼할 것이다.
at last...
결국...
This is her wish too.
이것은 그녀의 소원이기도 하다.
her...
그녀의...
hope?
소망?
Do you know the later Zhou of the Wu family?
우 가문의 후주를 아시나요?
no.
아니요.
I only met him once
난 그 사람을 딱 한 번 만났어요
At that time I did not know his identity.
그 당시 나는 그의 신원을 몰랐습니다.
I never thought we'd meet again.
우리가 다시 만날 거라고는 생각도 못했어요.
How is the investigation conducted?
조사는 어떻게 진행되나요?
In your father's case?
네 아버지 사건에?
In addition to mentioning
언급하는 것 외에도
How the Ge family committed fraud
Ge 가족이 어떻게 사기를 저질렀는지
My father wrote me a letter.
아버지는 나에게 편지로 말씀하셨다.
when he was in jail
그 사람이 감옥에 있었을 때
He received the following anonymous letter:
그는 다음과 같은 익명의 편지를 받았습니다.
“There is plenty of time ahead.
"앞으로 시간은 충분해요.
take care."
몸 조심하세요."
This person must know
이 사람은 꼭 알아야 해
Some inside information
일부 내부 정보
But I still don't know who that person is.
하지만 아직 그 사람이 누구인지는 알 수 없어요.
Why haven't I heard you mention it before?
왜 당신이 전에 그것에 대해 언급하는 것을 듣지 못했습니까?
me...
나...
Did you think I wasn't worthy of your trust?
내가 당신의 신뢰를 받을 가치가 없다고 생각했나요?
By the way, I reached
그건 그렇고, 나는 도달했습니다
The one who was my maid a few days ago.
며칠 전 내 하녀였던 사람.
She gave me a lot of information
그녀는 나에게 많은 정보를 제공했다
But most of them are useless.
하지만 대부분은 쓸모가 없습니다.
your maid?
당신의 하녀?
She was my family servant
그녀는 내 가족의 하인이었어
But it was sold to someone else.
하지만 다른 사람에게 팔렸습니다.
It took a lot of effort to find her.
그녀를 찾는데 많은 노력이 필요했어요
But she refused to be my maid again.
하지만 그 사람은 다시는 내 하녀가 되기를 거부했어요.
why?
왜?
Who knows?
누가 알아?
Ultimately, to each his own.
결국, 각자 자신에게.
You can't force anything.
아무것도 강요할 수 없습니다.
forced?
강요된?
great.
좋아요.
it's me.
나야.
Can we talk first?
먼저 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
I have nothing to say
할 말이 없다
To the junior lord of the Wu family.
우 가문의 후배 영주에게.
Are you angry?
당신은 화가 났습니까?
Because of my identity
내 정체성 때문에
Or because I hid my true identity from you?
아니면 내가 당신에게 내 진짜 신분을 숨겼기 때문에?
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Isn't it the same?
똑같지 않나요?
naught.
아무것도 아님.
I was just teasing you.
난 그냥 당신을 놀리고 있었어요.
What motivated you to come to me?
당신이 나에게 온 동기는 무엇입니까?
I swear
맹세해요
I fell in love with you at first sight
나는 첫눈에 당신과 사랑에 빠졌습니다
And I can't stop thinking about you.
그리고 당신에 대해 생각하는 것을 멈출 수 없습니다.
stop!
그만!
I am serious.
나는 진지하다.
It's like fate.
그것은 운명과 같습니다.
Since our first meeting, I cannot forget you.
첫 만남 이후로 나는 당신을 잊을 수 없습니다.
If this is all I want to say today
오늘 하고 싶은 말이 이게 전부라면
If so, you'd better leave now.
그렇다면 지금 떠나는 것이 좋습니다.
Do you really want to be with Zhong Yeran?
정말로 종예란과 함께 있고 싶나요?
It's better than being with you.
당신과 함께 있는 것보다 더 좋습니다.
He already has a wife.
그에게는 이미 아내가 있습니다.
Are you leaving or not?
떠날 거야, 말 거야?
If I told you
내가 만약 네게 말했다면
Can you erase your father's name?
네 아버지의 이름을 지울 수 있을까?
Do you think I will believe you?
내가 당신을 믿을 것이라고 생각합니까?
I'll count to three.
셋까지 셀게요.
If you don't go out, I'll scream.
안 나가면 소리 지르겠다.
Are you really going to do this?
정말 이걸 할 건가요?
one.
하나.
Have you ever wondered why I keep bothering you?
내가 왜 계속 당신을 괴롭히는지 궁금하지 않았나요?
two.
둘.
You will come to me in the future.
당신은 미래에 나에게 올 것입니다.
three.
삼.
master.
주인.
Do I still need to send an invitation?
그래도 초대장을 보내야 하나요?
To Mr. Jong?
종 씨에게?
She really doesn't seem to know.
그녀는 정말 모르는 것 같습니다.
yes. Send it to your servant's residence
예. 종 거주지로 보내세요
early in the morning tomorrow.
내일 아침 일찍.
what? Is there anything else?
무엇? 다른 것이 있나요?
master.
주인.
You found out the truth.
당신은 진실을 알아냈습니다.
Are you still going to take her?
아직도 그녀를 데려갈 건가요?
huh. she interests me
응. 그녀는 나에게 흥미를 준다
a little bit more.
점점 더.
But Mrs. Zhong is a married woman.
하지만 종 여사는 유부녀입니다.
I'm worried that he won't come out to see you.
그 사람이 당신을 만나러 나오지 않을까 걱정이에요.
I'll send her a proper invitation
나는 그녀에게 적절한 초대장을 보낼 거야
And that person is not a single woman.
그리고 그 사람은 미혼 여성이 아니거든요.
There is no reason for her not to meet me.
그녀가 나를 만나지 않을 이유가 없습니다.
Just send us a card.
카드를 보내주시면 됩니다.
What happens if she ignores it?
그녀가 그것을 무시하면 어떻게 되나요?
Then keep knocking on her door.
그럼 계속해서 그녀의 문을 두드리세요
Until she agrees.
그녀가 동의할 때까지.
After all, she and I have the same goals
결국 그녀와 나는 같은 목표를 가지고 있다
Not to mention how Zhong Yeran embarrassed her.
종예란이 그녀를 어떻게 당황하게 했는지는 말할 것도 없고
At the banquet that day.
그날 연회에서.
I don't think she'll say no
내 생각엔 그녀가 거절할 것 같지 않아
An ally like me.
나 같은 동맹자.
continue.
계속해.
Mistress, later wife of the Wu family
여주인, 우 가문의 후주
Send another invitation card.
다른 초대 카드를 보냅니다.
Just ignore it and throw the card aside.
그냥 무시하고 카드를 옆으로 버리세요.
government
정부
Why does he keep trying to talk to you?
그 사람은 왜 계속 너한테 말을 걸려고 하는 거지?
Maybe he thinks so
어쩌면 그 사람은 그렇게 생각할지도 몰라
we are suffering the same fate
우리는 같은 운명을 겪고 있다
And that we can do something together.
그리고 우리가 함께 뭔가를 할 수 있다는 것.
Don't listen to him, mistress.
그 사람 말을 듣지 마세요, 여주인님.
He seems to be making a plan.
그는 계획을 세우는 것 같습니다.
Of course not.
당연히 아니지.
How can you not see it?
어떻게 안 볼 수가 있지?
Because you realized that too?
너도 그걸 깨달았으니까?
I rejected him several times.
나는 그 사람을 여러 번 거절했어요.
But he won't give up.
하지만 그는 포기하지 않을 거예요.
No one loved him in his past life.
전생에 그를 사랑한 사람은 아무도 없었다.
Serves him well.
그에게 제대로 봉사합니다.
government.
정부.
Is that medicine for the skin?
그 약은 피부에 쓰는 약인가요?
But the smell is a little different.
그런데 냄새가 좀 달라요.
Don't get too close.
너무 가까이 다가가지 마세요.
Look how ignorant you are.
당신이 얼마나 무지한지보세요.
Qianzhi.
Qianzhi.
Yeoju made it herself.
여주가 직접 만들었어
So of course it's different.
그러니 당연히 다릅니다.
you are awesome
너 굉장하다.
You are good at everything, Mistress.
당신은 뭐든지 잘해요, 여주인님.
By the way, mistress, did you hear?
그런데 여주인님, 들으셨나요?
what?
무엇?
I heard Hwaman and a low-ranking maid.
화만과 하급 시녀를 들었다.
I made a mistake in the garden of bells.
종의 정원에서 실수를 저질렀다
The Lord gave it to the driver.
주님은 그것을 마부에게 주셨습니다.
They quietly left the city
그들은 조용히 도시를 떠났다
Early yesterday morning.
어제 아침 일찍.
I guess those people will never come back.
아무래도 그 사람들은 영원히 돌아올 수 없을 것 같아요.
A maid too?
하녀도요?
huh.
응.
I think we both made a mistake together
둘이 같이 실수한 것 같아
So both were punished.
그래서 둘 다 처벌을 받았습니다.
I heard the coachman came.
마부가 왔다고 들었는데
Nomads far from here.
여기서 멀리 떨어진 유목민.
This is his last delivery.
이번이 그의 마지막 배달이다
Then he will never come back.
그러면 그는 다시는 돌아오지 않을 것이다.
Mistress, what's going on?
여주인님, 무슨 일이에요?
Don’t you hate anger the most?
화만을 가장 싫어하지 않나요?
Get back to work.
다시 일하세요.
government
정부
Hwaman is responsible for attacking himself...
화만은 자신을 공격한 책임이 있다...
Lord.
주님.
She deserves it.
그녀는 그럴 자격이 있습니다.
Otherwise, at best you will be kicked out.
그렇지 않으면 기껏해야 쫓겨날 것이다.
I will go inside.
나는 안으로 들어갈 것이다.
It's a bit cold here.
여기는 좀 추워요.
Lord.
주님.
After the feast is over
향연이 끝난 후
The deacons left one by one.
집사들이 하나둘씩 떠나갔다
Within ten days.
열흘 안에.
But the descendants of the Wu family
하지만 우 가문의 후손
remain in the city
도시에 남아있다
Every day I visit my servant mistress.
매일 종 여주인을 방문합니다.
she refused to see him
그녀는 그를 만나기를 거부했다
But that didn't stop him.
하지만 그것이 그를 막지는 못했습니다.
His intentions are unclear.
그의 의도는 불분명하다.
He asked for a maid at the banquet.
그는 연회에서 하녀를 요청했다
And now he is trying to approach the servant mistress.
그리고 이제 그는 종 여주인에게 접근하려고 합니다.
This character is difficult to read.
읽기 힘든 캐릭터네요.
Lord, I...
주님, 제가...
How many days will Wu Shuomo stay?
Wu Shuomo는 며칠 동안 머물 예정인가요?
Lord, I was originally going to come here.
주님, 원래는 여기로 오려고 했는데요
For a month-long study tour.
한 달간의 스터디 투어를 위해.
But ten days have passed.
그런데 열흘이 지났다.
Then ignore him.
그럼 그를 무시하세요.
I want to see what he does.
나는 그가 무엇을 하는지 보고 싶다.
???five. ???Lady, let’s go.
???다섯. ???여주야, 가자.
seven. eight.
일곱. 여덟.
Mistress, please don't stay in your room all day.
여주인님, 하루종일 방에만 계시지 마세요.
You need to go outside and take a walk.
밖으로 나가서 산책을 해야 합니다.
???eleven. ???As you know
???열하나. ???아시다시피
Junior Woo is waiting outside.
우 후배가 밖에서 기다리고 있다고
I want to form an alliance with me.
나와 동맹을 맺고 싶어.
I'm afraid to go outside.
밖에 나가는 것이 두렵습니다.
I don't want to meet that person.
나는 그 사람을 만나고 싶지 않습니다.
But you can't sit in your room all day.
하지만 하루 종일 방에 앉아있을 수는 없습니다.
Why not play shuttlecock with us?
우리와 함께 셔틀콕을 쳐보는 건 어떨까요?
Maybe it will encourage you.
아마도 그것은 당신을 격려할 것입니다.
When I see you depressed every day
매일 우울해하는 널 보면
It makes us feel terrible.
우리를 끔찍한 기분으로 만듭니다.
huh.
응.
Join us.
우리와 함께하세요.
???right? ???let's play together.
???오른쪽? ???같이 놀자.
Join us, Mistress.
우리와 함께 하세요, 여주인님.
Come on, give it a try...
어서 해봐요...
So be it, Mistress.
그렇게 하세요, 여주인님.
here.
여기.
Are you okay, Guard Hua?
괜찮으세요, 경비병 후아?
???huh. ???go!
???응. ???가다!
let's go.
갑시다.
Are you sweating?
땀을 흘리고 있습니까?
Today is a hot day.
오늘은 무더운 날입니다.
Lady, if you are hot
여주야, 네가 더우면
Go inside and rest.
안으로 들어가서 쉬세요.
I've been in my room too long
너무 오랫동안 방에 있었어
And my body is getting weaker.
그리고 내 몸은 점점 약해지고 있어요.
It's great to enjoy the sun here.
여기서 태양을 즐기는 것이 좋습니다.
sure. Let me put this in there.
그럼요. 이것을 거기에 넣어 보겠습니다.
OK.
괜찮은.
Can you bring Hua Rongzhou here?
화룽저우(Hua Rongzhou)를 여기로 데려오실 수 있나요?
to me ...
나에게 ...
Let me try it.
내가 해보자.
Hello, mistress.
안녕하세요, 여주인님.
Rest in peace.
편안히 쉬십시오.
You don't have to bow to me
나한테 절할 필요는 없어
When it's just us.
우리만 있을 때.
Nothing special.
별거 없습니다.
i just see you
난 단지 당신을 볼 뿐입니다
We guard the entrance here every day.
매일 이곳에서 입구를 지키고 있어요
And no one takes turns with you.
그리고 아무도 당신과 교대로 참여하지 않습니다.
i just want to tell you
난 단지 당신에게 말하고 싶어
The idea is that you can come here once every two days.
이틀에 한 번 여기에 올 수 있다는 것입니다.
I am the guard of your house, mistress.
저는 당신 집의 경비병입니다, 여주인님.
How do I leave a post without permission?
승인 없이 게시물을 남기려면 어떻게 해야 하나요?
are you okay.
괜찮아요.
There are too many guards coming and going.
오고가는 경비원이 너무 많습니다.
Nothing bad will happen.
나쁜 일은 일어나지 않을 것입니다.
Life is short.
인생은 짧다.
And you are too young.
그리고 당신은 너무 어려요.
There must be something you want to do.
꼭 하고 싶은 일이 있을 겁니다.
Don't waste your time working as a security guard.
경비원으로 일하는 데 시간을 낭비하지 마십시오.
What do I want to do?
내가 하고 싶은 일이요?
huh. do what you want
응. 네가 원하는 것을해라.
I will send it to you if you need it.
필요하시면 보내드리겠습니다.
How rare!
얼마나 희귀한가!
I didn't expect to see him here.
나는 그를 여기서 볼 것이라고 기대하지 않았습니다.
huh.
응.
I thought he was too afraid to come here.
나는 그가 여기 오기를 너무 두려워한다고 생각했습니다.
You already look like a woman
벌써 여자로 보이네
And he hangs out with women every day.
그리고 그는 매일 여자들과 어울린다.
???Want to spar? ???I think it's good.
???스파링하고 싶어? ???좋은 것 같아요.
Bring it.
그것을 가져와.
Would you like to join them?
그들과 함께 하시겠습니까?
???huh. It's easy. Take your time. ???Stop!
???응. 쉬운 일이지. 천천히 해요. ???멈추다!
Not me. I'm not going to argue with you.
나는 아니다. 나는 당신과 논쟁하지 않을 것입니다.
Good move!
좋은 움직임입니다!
I knew you were a good person when I hired you.
나는 채용 당시 당신이 좋은 사람이라는 것을 알았습니다.
let's face you
당신과 대적하자
And see how much progress we have made
그리고 얼마나 발전했는지 확인해보세요
Over the past few months.
지난 몇 달 동안.
Yes, Director.
네, 국장님.
The needle should go in here.
바늘은 여기로 들어가야 합니다.
Make the snitch smaller.
스니치를 더 작게 만드세요.
Yeoju, how about getting some rest?
여주야, 좀 쉬는 게 어때?
And are you going to continue another day?
그리고 다른 날을 계속할 건가요?
government.
정부.
I heard there was a fight at the training ground.
훈련장에서 싸움이 났다고 들었어
And Guard Hua was very skillful.
그리고 Guard Hua는 매우 능숙했습니다.
He even defeated veterans.
그는 심지어 베테랑들을 물리쳤다.
really?
정말?
He's only been here for half a year, right?
그 사람 여기에 온 지 반년밖에 안 됐어요, 그렇죠?
You will be surprised, Mistress.
놀라실 겁니다, 여주인님.
Teacher also praised me today.
오늘은 스승님도 칭찬해 주셨네요
He said he drew a picture with Nan Feng.
난펑과 함께 그림을 그렸다고 하더군요
After learning a few moves from him.
그에게서 몇 가지 동작을 배운 후.
The moment you make eye contact with that person
그 사람과 눈이 마주친 순간
I knew he was someone special.
나는 그가 특별한 사람이라는 것을 알았습니다.
Because Nan Feng hesitated.
난펑이 주저했기 때문이다.
You are a single girl.
당신은 미혼 소녀입니다.
Aren’t you embarrassed to say that?
그런 말을 하는 게 부끄럽지 않나요?
Nanfeng is the highest ranking security guard.
Nanfeng은 가장 높은 순위의 경비원입니다.
So he must be good at martial arts.
그러니까 그 사람은 무술을 잘하는 게 틀림없어요.
huh.
응.
So that means Guard Hua is really good.
그러니 Guard Hua가 정말 뛰어나다는 뜻이죠.
How shameless.
얼마나 뻔뻔한가.
???Don't say that! ???You are shameless.
???그렇게 말하지 마세요! ???당신은 뻔뻔해요.
???Stop talking about that! ???you are!
???그 얘긴 그만해! ???당신은!
You... that's not true at all.
당신... 그건 전혀 사실이 아닙니다.
Mr. Huarongzhou, come here.
화룽저우 씨, 이리 오세요.
government.
정부.
Did something good happen?
좋은 일 있었나요?
I feel good.
기분이 좋은 것 같습니다.
You finally remember my name, Mistress.
드디어 내 이름을 기억하시네요, 여주인님.
Have I forgotten anything?
내가 잊어버린 적 있나요?
I heard it from Chuiju.
추이주한테 들었어
What you drew with Nanfeng
당신이 Nanfeng으로 그린 ​​것
In a sparring session.
스파링 세션에서.
I think it's because the team leader blocked it.
아무래도 팀장님이 막았기 때문인 것 같아요.
Not only is he talented in martial arts;
무술에 재능이 있을 뿐만 아니라
But you are also humble.
하지만 당신은 또한 겸손합니다.
Cuizhu tastes good.
Cuizhu는 맛이 좋습니다.
government.
정부.
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
Where are the best artisan shops in the city?
이 도시 최고의 장인 가게는 어디에 있나요?
I heard there is a female craftsman.
여자 장인이 있다고 들었는데
My name is Wei Xian.
웨이 시안(Wei Xian)이라고 합니다.
She was the most skilled.
그녀는 가장 숙련된 사람이었습니다.
Female craftsman?
여성 장인?
I have never heard of this person.
나는 이 사람에 대해 들어본 적이 없습니다.
Don't you know him, mistress?
당신은 그 사람을 모르시나요, 여주인님?
All the girls admired her.
모든 소녀들이 그녀를 존경했습니다.
Unfortunately, she passed away not long ago.
안타깝게도 그녀는 얼마 전 세상을 떠났습니다.
I don't know what other stores are like.
다른 매장은 어떨지 모르겠네요.
Should I ask guard Hua around?
경비병 Hua에게 주변에 물어볼까?
no. Don't tell that person.
아뇨. 그 사람에게 말하지 마세요.
Go ask in person
직접 가서 물어보세요
And quickly.
그리고 빨리.
OK.
괜찮은.
Have you returned from training?
훈련을 마치고 돌아오셨나요?
We are eating and drinking.
우리는 먹고 마시고 있어요.
Want to join us?
우리와 함께하고 싶나요?
Are you sure you don't want to?
정말 원하지 않나요?
???Please eat. ??? Have some with us.
???드세요. ??? 우리와 함께 좀 드세요.
Look how rebellious he is.
그가 얼마나 반항적인지 보세요.
What else can you do?
또 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
He is skilled in martial arts.
그는 무술에 능숙합니다.
I think it's because the boss was generous.
사장님이 관대하셨기 때문인 것 같아요.
He persevered and it ended up being a tie.
그는 참았고 그것이 결국 동점으로 끝났습니다.
I think it's unclear who stopped it.
누가 막았는지 불분명하다고 생각합니다.
Let's throw it away.
그것을 버리자.
No more about that grumpy man.
그 심술궂은 남자에 대해서는 이제 그만.
Go ahead and try it. Drink.
어서 해봐요. 마셔 라.
Let's talk about the team leader
팀장님 얘기를 하자면
Did you hear the rumor?
소문 들었어?
Are you talking about something related to Mistress?
Mistress와 관련된 것을 말씀하시는 건가요?
???Lower your voice. ???not needed.
???목소리를 낮추세요. ???필요 없음.
Everyone at home knows it.
집에 있는 사람들은 모두 그 사실을 알고 있습니다.
???Quiet. ???But yes.
???조용히 해. ???하지만 그렇습니다.
When Master Ordered Us to Cut Expenses
스승님이 지출을 삭감하라고 명령하셨을 때
The chief went straight to Deacon Ji.
서장은 곧바로 지집사에게 갔다.
To reason with him.
그와 추리하기 위해.
He is the Master's personal guard. How did he...
그는 마스터의 개인 경비원입니다. 그가 어떻게...
I really can't believe it.
정말 믿을 수가 없어요.
enough...
충분한...
It's not a good thing.
좋은 일이 아닙니다.
Don't talk about it anymore. Let's drink.
더 이상 그것에 대해 이야기하지 마십시오. 마시자.
He still can't see me?
그 사람 아직도 날 못 볼 거에요?
No, she won't.
아니, 그녀는 그러지 않을 것이다.
Mr. Jong says he is not feeling well.
종 씨는 자신이 몸이 좋지 않다고 말합니다.
To welcome guests.
손님을 맞이하기 위해.
Is he unwell?
그 사람 몸이 안 좋나요?
But when I saw her, she seemed full of energy.
하지만 내가 봤을 때 그녀는 활력이 넘쳐 보였다.
Before coming to Hwangcheong
황청에 오기 전
You promised to come here
너 여기 오기로 약속했잖아
formula for
공식에 대한
Jiayin Pill of the Zhong family.
Zhong 가족의 Jiayin Pill.
A month and a half has passed.
한달 반이 지났습니다.
Instead of searching for the formula
공식을 검색하는 대신
You are looking for someone.
당신은 누군가를 찾고 있습니다.
If you know this...
선배님이 이 사실을 아신다면...
Please don't use my father to threaten me.
아버지를 이용하여 나를 위협하지 마십시오.
Who is your master?
당신의 주인은 누구입니까?
Of course, it's you.
물론, 당신입니다.
But we have to go back in ten days
하지만 우리는 열흘 뒤에 다시 돌아가야 해
So let's just forget about it.
그러니 그냥 잊어버리자.
I'll find someone else who can help me.
나에게 도움을 줄 수 있는 다른 사람을 찾아보겠습니다.
Enjoy and drink as much as you like.
원하는 만큼 즐기고 마시세요.
This is my treat.
이것이 나의 대접입니다.
Your generosity is worthy of your status.
당신의 관대함은 당신의 지위에 걸맞습니다
The son of the Jong clan deacon.
종씨 집사의 아들.
I am the only son of my parents.
나는 부모님의 유일한 아들입니다.
And everything my father owns
그리고 내 아버지가 소유한 모든 것은
It will be mine.
내 것이 될 것이다.
Not to mention serving you a meal.
당신에게 식사를 대접하는 것은 말할 것도 없습니다.
great.
좋아요.
It's really rare to see Miss Jiaojiao.
Miss Jiaojiao를 보는 것은 정말 드뭅니다.
You are truly amazing! I'm impressed.
당신은 정말 대단해요! 나는 감동.
Zhao Zhao.
자오자오.
You weren't around. This is nothing.
당신은 주변에 없었습니다. 이것은 아무것도 아니다.
How bold! who are you?
얼마나 대담한가! 누구세요?
It's you, Lord Wu Junior.
바로 당신입니다, 우 주니어 영주님.
It's really you, Hua Young Master.
정말 당신이군요, Hua Young Master.
I thought I heard wrong
내가 잘못 들은 줄 알았는데
When I was standing in front of the door.
내가 문 앞에 서 있었을 때.
This is the junior lord of the Wu family.
이것은 우 가문의 후배 영주입니다.
???nice to meet you. ???nice to meet you.
???만나서 반가워요. ???만나서 반가워요.
???Please sit down. ???please.
???앉아주세요. ???제발.
hurry.
빨리.
Master Hwayoung
화영 스승님
you left a deep impression on me
당신은 나에게 깊은 인상을 남겼습니다
At the feast.
향연에서.
I wanted to make friends with you
나는 당신과 친구를 만들고 싶었어요
But I couldn't find a good way to reach you.
하지만 당신에게 다가갈 좋은 방법을 찾지 못했습니다.
Oh, I'm so happy.
아, 정말 기쁘네요.
I also felt like you were an old friend.
나도 당신이 오랜 친구인 것 같았어요
At the first meeting.
첫 번째 회의에서.
exactly.
정확히.
???Yes... nice to meet you. ???Cheers.
???네... 만나서 반가워요. ???건배.
Go ahead and try it.
어서 해봐요.
Jiaojiao, go and serve Junior Lord Wu.
Jiaojiao, 가서 Wu Junior Lord를 섬기십시오.
???not needed. ???Space.
???필요 없음. ???우주님.
Such an ignorant woman
이런 무식한 여자
Not my type.
내 타입이 아니야.
Go back to where you were.
당신이 있던 곳으로 돌아가십시오.
Come on, let's drink.
자, 마시자.
Junior Woo, are you talking about this?
우 후배님, 말씀하시는 겁니까?
you can't forget
당신은 잊을 수 없습니다
Teacher Jong’s maid?
종 선생님의 하녀?
That's sad
안타깝네요
Someone stopped me.
누군가 나를 막았다고.
I think
제 생각에는
My brother-in-law has gone too far.
내 처남이 너무 멀리 갔어.
She is just a housekeeper.
그녀는 단지 가정부입니다.
Why can't he give her to you?
그 사람은 왜 그녀를 당신에게 줄 수 없나요?
He already has my sister as his wife.
그 사람은 이미 내 여동생을 아내로 두고 있어요.
Why is he still thinking about other women?
왜 그는 아직도 다른 여자를 생각하는 걸까요?
exactly.
정확히.
Ms. Zhong is the most talented woman
종 여사는 가장 재능있는 여성입니다
city
도시
And it is famous all over the world.
그리고 전 세계적으로 유명해요.
Teacher Zhong doesn't taste good.
종 선생님은 맛이 좋지 않습니다.
It's a shame it came late
늦게 와서 아쉽다
And she's already married to him.
그리고 그녀는 이미 그와 결혼했어요.
Otherwise I will compete with him.
그렇지 않으면 나는 그와 경쟁할 것이다.
I couldn't agree more.
나는 더 이상 동의할 수 없었다.
My sister is the prettiest girl in the world.
내 여동생은 세상에서 가장 예쁜 여자야.
Who can compare to her?
누가 그녀와 비교할 수 있습니까?
Can you do it?
할 수 있나요?
You are stating the obvious.
당신은 명백한 것을 말하고 있습니다.
Anyway, if my father didn't stop me
어쨌든, 아버지가 나를 말리지 않으셨다면
I would have rushed to the servant's residence.
나는 종 거주지로 달려갔을 것이다
And beat up Mr. Jong.
그리고 종 선생님을 구타하세요.
Exactly my feelings!
내 감정이 딱!
as it were
말하자면
I would like to speak with Mrs. Zhong.
종 여사님과 이야기하고 싶습니다.
If she lets me take the maid
만약 그녀가 내가 하녀를 데려가도록 허락한다면
Then the thorn in your side will be pulled out.
그러면 옆구리에 있는 가시가 뽑힐 것이다
Then he will be able to live more comfortably.
그러면 그 사람은 좀 더 편안하게 살 수 있을 거야
In the species residence. Am I right?
종 거주지에서. 내가 맞나요?
my sister is smart
내 여동생은 똑똑해요
But I don't think he can make a decision
하지만 내 생각엔 그 사람이 결정을 내릴 수 없을 것 같아
For my brother-in-law.
내 처남을 위해.
It's not difficult
어렵지 않아요
It's about finding a way to satisfy both.
두 가지 모두를 만족시킬 수 있는 방법을 찾는 것입니다.
But Ms. Jong
하지만 종 여사는
stay at home for a while
한동안 집에 머물다.
I’m curious, Master Hwayoung...
궁금해요, 화영 스승님...
Hua brother...
화 형님...
If you could introduce me to her.
만약 당신이 그녀에게 나를 소개할 수 있다면.
Look at your face. It's so red.
당신의 얼굴을보세요. 너무 빨개요.
Furong is so pretty.
푸롱이 참 예쁘네요.
I beg to differ.
나는 다르게 간청한다.
???She is mine. ???There are even prettier ones.
???그녀는 내 꺼야. ???더 예쁜 것도 있어요.
she is mine
그녀는 내 꺼야.
Woo Junior Road
우 주니어 로드
Are you really not going to my house?
너 정말 우리 집에 안 갈 거야?
no.
아니요.
Then we will leave.
그럼 우리는 떠날 거예요.
???goodbye. ???goodbye.
???안녕히 가세요. ???안녕히 가세요.
???is... ???I'm telling you
???가... ???내가 말하는데
Huang prepared dinner for us.
Huang은 우리를 위해 저녁 식사를 준비했습니다.
Let's keep drinking.
계속 마시자.
???Let’s drink! ???Furong is mine.
???마시자! ???푸롱은 내꺼야.
???right. She is yours. ???master.
???오른쪽. 그녀는 당신 것입니다. ???주인.
???How are you? ???She is mine.
???어떻게 지내요? ???그녀는 내 꺼야.
Brother Hua, can you introduce her to me?
Hua 형제님, 저에게 그녀를 소개해 주실 수 있나요?
I can't make decisions for her.
나는 그녀를 위해 결정을 내릴 수 없습니다.
She is a very independent woman.
그녀는 매우 독립적인 여성입니다.
If I do that without telling her
만약 내가 그녀에게 말하지 않고 그런 짓을 한다면
She will be angry.
그녀는 화를 낼 것입니다.
She is no ordinary woman.
그녀는 평범한 여자가 아닙니다.
When Zhao Jiao gets angry
자오자오가 화가 나면
All I have to do is buy her cosmetics.
내가 해야 할 일은 그녀에게 화장품을 사주는 것뿐이다.
But my sister is different.
하지만 언니는 달라요.
If I make her angry
내가 그녀를 화나게 하면
That person will ignore me
그 사람은 날 무시할 거야
No matter how much jewelry I buy her.
내가 그녀에게 얼마나 많은 보석을 사주든 간에.
That guy looks stupid
그 사람 바보 같아 보여요
But in reality, that's not the case.
하지만 실제로는 그렇지 않습니다.
if there is no other way
다른 방법이 없다면
I will have to sneak into the servant's residence myself.
내가 직접 종 거주지로 몰래 들어가야겠습니다.
Chong Residence
종 레지던스
Because you came here today
오늘 당신이 여기 왔으니까
Let's spar one more round.
한 라운드 더 스파링하자.
I will show no mercy this time.
이번에는 자비를 베풀지 않겠습니다.
He is the Master's personal guard. How did he...
그는 마스터의 개인 경비원입니다. 그가 어떻게...
I can't believe it.
믿을 수 없군.
OK.
괜찮은.
remember.
기억하다.
Let me stop before I go too far.
너무 멀리 가기 전에 멈추겠습니다.
no.
아니요.
Well done.
잘하셨어요.
Just as I expected.
내가 예상했던 대로.
You didn't give it up last time.
당신은 지난번에 그것을 포기하지 않았습니다.
why?
왜?
Please forgive me, Director.
용서해주세요, 국장님.
Tell me please. Why did you endure it?
말해 주세요. 왜 참았어?
You fought with me last time, right?
지난번에 나랑 싸웠지?
person
사람
the person who taught me martial arts
나에게 무술을 가르쳐 준 사람
He told me to do that.
그렇게 하라고 하더군요.
Are you a martial arts teacher?
무술 선생님이요?
What does he do?
그는 무엇을 하는가?
Forget it. I'll tell the master right now
잊어 버려. 지금 당장 마스터한테 말해볼게
They recruited a martial arts genius.
무술 천재를 영입했다는 것이다.
Go ahead and try it! Welcome back, our victor!
어서 해봐요! 돌아온 걸 환영해요, 우리의 승리자님!
Welcome back...
돌아온 것을 환영합니다...
You are truly amazing, Guard Hua.
당신은 정말 대단해요, Guard Hua.
OK.
괜찮은.
Lady, do you have something to say to me?
여주야, 나한테 할 말 있어?
yes. we all heard
예. 우리 모두 들었어
You beat Nanfeng today.
당신이 오늘 Nanfeng을 이겼다고요.
huh. So we are celebrating for you.
응. 그래서 우리는 당신을 위해 축하하고 있습니다.
???Qianzhi.???Yes, teacher.
???Qianzhi.???네, 선생님.
government.
정부.
This is a reward for you.
이것은 당신을 위한 보상입니다.
Open it.
열어 봐.
This is custom made
이건 맞춤 제작이에요
From the best stores in town.
도시 최고의 매장에서.
I see you are still using it.
아직도 사용하고 계신 걸 봤어요
Home-issued saber.
집에서 발행한 세이버.
Now you are the only guard in my house
이제 당신은 내 집의 유일한 경비원입니다
needless to mention
언급 할 필요없는
Your skills are on par with Nanfeng.
당신의 기술은 Nanfeng과 동등하다고
So we cannot make you use inferior weapons.
그래서 우리는 당신이 열등한 무기를 사용하도록 할 수 없습니다.
you work for me
당신은 나를 위해 일합니다
And I promise you won't be disappointed.
그리고 나는 당신이 실망하지 않을 것이라고 약속합니다.
You can get anything you want.
당신은 당신이 원하는 무엇이든 얻을 수 있습니다.
What did you do? Who did that?
뭐 했어? 누가 그랬나요?
Why are there so many flower petals on the ground?
땅에 꽃잎이 왜 이렇게 많아?
I just went out for a moment
그냥 잠깐 나갔다왔어
And you turned this place upside down.
그리고 당신은 이곳을 뒤집어 놓았습니다.
Hurry up and clean up the mess.
서둘러서 난장판을 정리하세요.
???soon! ???I will do it now.
???곧! ???이제 할게요.
Bring a broom.
빗자루를 가져와.
gaga. broomstick.
가, 가. 빗자루.
huh. hurry.
응. 빨리.
These girls...
이 소녀들...
My throat really hurts.
정말 목이 아프다.
thank you
감사합니다.
Thank you, Mistress.
고마워요, 여주인님.
are you okay. hope you like it
괜찮아요. 너가 좋아하길 바래.
This is my first time receiving a gift.
선물을 받은 건 이번이 처음이에요.
I like it very much.
나는 그것을 아주 많이 좋아.
Has nothing changed in the last half month?
지난 반달 동안 아무것도 바뀌지 않았나요?
yes.
예.
It seems like they are the master and the mistress.
주인과 여주인인 것 같습니다.
We haven't talked to each other much these days.
요즘 서로 말을 많이 하지 않았어요.
They're still mad at each other.
그들은 여전히 ​​서로에게 화를 내고 있습니다.
I do not know.
모르겠습니다.
Go and talk to the magistrate.
가서 치안에게 말해요
To come tomorrow.
내일 오려고.
I will ask her about it.
나는 그녀에게 그것에 대해 물어볼 것이다.
Your Majesty, didn't you tell me?
전하, 말씀하시지 않았나요?
Was it your job?
스승님의 일이었나요?
Would you like to do something about it now?
이제 그것에 대해 뭔가 조치를 취하시겠습니까?
majesty.
전하.
Is the wedding over?
결혼식은 끝났나요?
I heard Master was drunk.
스승님이 취하셨다고 들었어
Last night I slept in his study.
어젯밤에는 그의 서재에서 잤어요.
He can't blame it on anyone.
그는 그것을 누구에게도 비난할 수 없습니다.
That guy was pretty stupid to fall for that trick.
그 사람은 그 속임수에 넘어가기엔 꽤 멍청했어요.
because you know about it
당신이 그것에 대해 알고 있기 때문에
Why didn't you tell him, Your Majesty?
왜 그에게 말하지 않았습니까, 전하?
Perhaps he changed his mind.
아마도 그는 마음을 바꾸었을 것입니다.
That's his job.
그건 그 사람의 일이에요
and he is sure of it
그리고 그는 그것을 확신한다
daughter of the fah family
화씨 가문의 딸
Innocent and kind.
순진하고 친절해요.
There is no evidence
증거가 없어요
So what can I say?
그럼 내가 무슨 말을 할 수 있겠어?
It won't be easy for the Master.
마스터에게는 쉽지 않을 겁니다.
Let's hope Hua Qian stops
Hua Qian이 멈추길 바라자
I'm doing that
그런 짓을 하고 있어
You will never cause us any trouble again.
다시는 우리에게 문제를 일으키지 않을 것입니다.
How did the young woman like her
젊은 여자는 어떻게 그녀를 좋아했는가
Learn these dirty tricks?
이런 더러운 속임수를 배워?
Now that they're married
이제 그들은 결혼했으니
I think she gradually
내 생각에 그녀는 점차적으로
You become more mature and calm.
더욱 성숙해지고 차분해집니다.
We'll see.
우리는 보게 될 것이다.
When you come here tomorrow to say hello to me
내일 나한테 인사하러 여기 올 때
We'll have to see how much she matures.
그녀가 얼마나 성숙해졌는지 지켜봐야겠습니다.
most people come to my house
대부분의 사람들이 내 집에 온다
Because they want something.
왜냐하면 그들은 무언가를 원하기 때문입니다.
There are very few people
사람이 거의 없어요
A person who wants nothing.
아무것도 원하지 않는 사람.
All she does is talk to me.
그녀가 하는 일은 나와 이야기하는 것 뿐이다.
I can talk freely with her.
나는 그녀와 자유롭게 이야기할 수 있다.
OK.
괜찮은.
I'll call someone and have them talk to her.
나는 누군가를 불러서 그녀에게 말하게 할 것이다.
Please continue.
계속하세요.
Is this news trustworthy?
이 뉴스는 믿을만한가요?
Teacher, that's right.
선생님, 그렇죠.
It's great.
훌륭해요.
It seems like she has nowhere to run this time.
이번에는 그녀가 달릴 곳이 없는 것 같아요.
Hello, mistress.
안녕하세요, 여주인님.
sit down please.
앉아 요.
Yes, mistress.
네, 여주인님.
I heard you weren't there
나는 당신이 없었다고 들었습니다
I went out of the house a few days ago.
며칠전 집밖으로 나갔다.
I felt tired
나는 피곤함을 느꼈다
So I just stayed at home.
그래서 그냥 집에 있었어요.
That's not good.
그 좋지 않다.
As the mistress of the head family
종가의 여주인으로서
You have a duty to improve Yelan's reputation
당신은 옐란의 명성을 높일 의무가 있습니다
So, you should go out and socialize more often.
그러니 더 자주 나가서 사교 활동을 해야 합니다.
hostess
여주인
She shouldn't be confined to her house.
그녀의 집에만 갇혀 있어서는 안 된다.
She needs to interact often.
그녀는 자주 교류해야 한다
Along with the wives of other prominent men.
다른 저명한 남자들의 아내들과 함께.
yes.
예.
one more.
하나 더.
You need to pay more attention
좀 더 주의를 기울이셔야 해요
About what Yellen did
옐런이 한 일에 대해
At the feast.
향연에서.
you are too young
넌 너무 어려.
There are many things you don't understand.
당신이 이해하지 못하는 많은 것들이 있습니다.
feelings of love or gratitude
사랑이나 감사의 감정
between a couple
부부 사이
It tends to fade over time.
시간이 지남에 따라 퇴색되는 경향이 있습니다.
hold tightly in one's hands
손에 힘을 단단히 쥐다
It's the key to a long-lasting marriage.
오래 지속되는 결혼 생활의 열쇠입니다.
Thank you for your advice, Mistress.
조언 감사드립니다, 여주인님.
That maid’s name is Mu Yao, right?
그 하녀 이름이 무야오 맞죠?
How are you going to treat her?
그녀를 어떻게 대할 건가요?
The teacher likes her.
선생님은 그녀를 좋아해요.
I don't want to go against his wishes.
나는 그의 뜻에 어긋나고 싶지 않습니다.
You should carefully monitor what is going on at home.
집에 있는 일들을 주의 깊게 관찰해야 합니다.
Otherwise, even a housekeeper
그렇지 않으면 가정부라도
It was able to climb onto its owner's bed.
주인의 침대 위로 기어올라갈 수 있었습니다.
Mu Yao is not that kind of person.
무야오는 그런 사람이 아니다.
Your Majesty, you have no idea.
전하, 당신은 전혀 모릅니다.
Mu Yao has never tempted Master.
무야오는 단 한 번도 스승님을 유혹한 적이 없습니다.
You'll stop thinking like this
이런 생각은 그만 하게 될 거야
When you meet Mu Yao.
Mu Yao를 만나면.
Why are you still taking his side?
왜 아직도 그 사람 편을 드는 거야?
I'm just stating the truth.
나는 단지 사실을 말하고 있을 뿐입니다.
I hope you don't misjudge anyone.
나는 당신이 누군가를 잘못 판단하지 않기를 바랍니다.
Why is it so soft?
왜 이렇게 부드러워졌나요?
That's reality.
그것이 현실입니다.
It's no use fighting.
내가 싸워봤자 소용없어요.
You almost lost your life saving Yelan.
당신은 옐란을 구하다가 목숨을 잃을 뻔했습니다.
This time we went too far.
이번에는 너무 멀리 갔다.
you are his lawful wife
당신은 그의 합법적인 아내입니다
So he shouldn't have done this to you.
그러니까 그 사람이 너한테 이런 짓을 하면 안 됐어.
If you feel like you can't speak
말을 할 수 없을 것 같다면
I'll talk to him on your behalf.
내가 당신을 대신해서 그 사람과 얘기해 볼게요.
Mistress, you know how, right?
여주인님, 방법 아시죠?
I married Master, right?
저는 스승님과 결혼했어요, 그렇죠?
you...
너...
Don't change the subject.
주제를 바꾸지 마세요.
I'm talking about maids.
나는 하녀에 대해 이야기하고 있습니다.
as his lawful wife
그의 합법적인 아내로서
You must assert your authority.
당신은 당신의 권위를 주장해야합니다.
You should not sit still and do nothing.
아무것도 하지 않고 가만히 있어서는 안 됩니다.
Mistress, may I pass on your orders?
여주인님, 명령을 전해드려도 될까요?
What order?
무슨 순서인가요?
Master and Mu Yao fell in love with each other.
스승님과 무야오가 서로 사랑에 빠졌어요
Then could you please give me an order?
그럼 명령을 내려주시겠어요?
To make her your master's concubine?
그녀를 주인의 첩으로 만들려고?
you...
너...
you are...
당신은...
Do you really mean that?
정말 그런 뜻인가요?
yes.
예.
She will just be a concubine.
그녀는 단지 첩이 될 것입니다.
You are his lawful wife.
당신은 그의 합법적인 아내입니다.
I'll leave the decision up to you.
결정은 여러분에게 맡기겠습니다.
But could you do something for me?
하지만 저를 위해 좀 해주시겠어요?
Otherwise, Master may get the wrong idea.
그렇지 않으면 스승님께서 잘못된 생각을 하실 수도 있습니다.
OK.
괜찮은.
Your wish has come true.
당신의 소원이 이루어졌습니다.
I'll send someone to the servant's residence tomorrow.
내일 종 거주지로 사람을 보내겠습니다
Deliver commands.
명령을 전달합니다.
Thank you so much, ma'am.
정말 감사합니다, 여주인님.
Please eat some of this.
이것 좀 드세요.
I have a good appetite today, Your Majesty.
오늘은 식욕이 좋습니다, 전하.
A heavy burden was lifted off my shoulders
내 어깨에서 무거운 짐이 내려졌어
So I feel much better.
그래서 기분이 훨씬 좋아졌어요.
Because she suggested that
그녀가 그런 제안을 했기 때문에
Yelan marries a concubine
옐란, 첩과 결혼하다
That means
그 뜻은
She wants to get back together with him.
그녀는 그와 다시 만나고 싶어합니다.
It's true.
그것은 사실이다.
The hostess is really giving.
여주인은 정말로 기부하고 있습니다.
she has to find out
그녀는 알아내야 해
How to run a household alone.
혼자서 집안을 운영하는 방법.
We all learn from painful experiences
우리 모두는 고통스러운 경험을 통해 배운다
At best I can give you some advice.
나는 기껏해야 어느 정도 조언을 드릴 수 있습니다.
I'm glad she heeded my advice.
그녀가 내 조언에 귀를 기울인 것이 기쁘다.
yes. Your Majesty, you proposed to her
예. 전하, 당신은 그녀에게 제안했습니다
Valuable advice.
귀중한 조언.
Don't butter me.
나에게 버터를 바르지 마세요.
Madam, why did you ask Your Majesty?
여주인님, 전하께 왜 물으셨나요?
Are you trying to take a concubine for your master?
스승님을 위해 첩을 취하려고?
You are too kind to Mu Yao.
당신은 Mu Yao에게 너무 친절해요.
It just occurred to me
방금 나한테 그런 생각이 들었어
There was a simple and direct way
간단하고 직접적인 방법이 있었다는 걸
I'm trying to make Jong Ye-ran understand something.
종예란에게 뭔가를 이해시키려고요.
What do you understand?
뭘 이해해?
There's no room for the two of us.
우리 둘이 들어갈 공간이 없어요.
I’ll make your wedding a grand one too.
결혼식도 성대하게 해줄게
When he took her as his concubine
그가 그녀를 첩으로 삼았을 때
Then he will know too
그러면 그 사람도 알게 될 거야
He can't avoid problems.
그는 문제를 피할 수 없습니다.
he knows it
그는 그것을 알고 있다
Mu Yao and I can never share a husband.
무야오와 나는 결코 남편을 공유할 수 없습니다.
So if he wants to live a chaotic life
그러니 그가 혼란스러운 삶을 살고 싶다면
He can keep me locked up in the servant residence.
그는 나를 계속해서 종 거주지에 가두어 둘 수 있습니다.
Mistress, why don't you just kick him out?
여주인님, 그냥 그 사람을 쫓아내시는 게 어때요?
Why you should take it while lying down
누워서 복용해야 하는 이유
And will it make her happy?
그리고 그녀를 행복하게 해줄까?
Do you kick her out?
그녀를 쫓아내나요?
Easier said than done.
말은 말처럼 쉽지 않습니다.
They are like two magnets.
그들은 두 개의 자석과 같습니다.
The more I try to separate
분리하려고 하면 할수록
It gets harder and harder.
점점 더 단단해집니다.
Is it Mr. Zhong in the front carriage?
앞 마차에 종씨씨인가요?
Lord, those problems are solved.
주님, 그 문제들은 해결되었습니다.
go to the doctor and get me
의사에게 가서 나를 데려오세요
Another bottle of evolution powder.
진화가루 한병 더.
Lord, are you not feeling well?
주님 몸이 안 좋으신가요?
I'm doing great. It's just...
잘 지내요. 그것은 단지 ...
For emergency situations.
긴급 상황을 위해.
Give orders to Lin Jiang.
Lin Jiang에게 명령을 내리십시오.
Manager Gao, are you sure about this?
가오 청지기님, 이거 확실해요?
The Lord has made up his mind.
주님께서 마음을 정하셨습니다.
And we shouldn't question him.
그리고 우리는 그에게 질문을 해서는 안 됩니다.
just do it.
그냥 해.